# **Eugene Durov**

Digital product designer with 10+ years of all-around experience in design with a frontend development background.

Last few years I have been working on B2B projects, but I am open to offers in various design fields.

Saint Petersburg +7 981 734 27 96 <u>artewgen@gmail.com</u>

behance.net/artewgen

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Product Designer at YooMoney (ex. Yandex.Money)

AUG 2019 - Present, Saint Petersburg

Responsible for the full design processes of payment solutions from the first idea to launching. During my work, I redesigned projects such as the Embedded checkout form, Redirect form and Mobile SDK. Modernization of Widget (Embedded form) is the most successful project — the conversion rate increased by more than 5% and the concept of the widget was re-used in more than 8 company projects. Also, I implemented a new method in payment forms — SberPay.

Worked with B2C and launched a utility bills project.

Other responsibilities:

- Conducting user researches: interviews and usability testings;
- Taking an active role in the sprints planning for the front-end team for effective production of services and using scrum methodology;
- Developing a design system.

### Product Designer at Yandex

MAY 2019 – AUG 2019, Moscow

Participated in designing several intranet tools (VConf, Staff and Femida). Fully redesigned internal video conference service VConf — now it's one of the main tools of Yandex internal communication.

# UX/UI Designer | Frontend Developer at Personal Projects

SEP 2014 – MAY 2019, Minsk

Design and frontend development with a small team. The most successful projects:

- Web aggregator of popular Instagram profiles with a subscription to them. The service was visited by more than 150 thousand users per month and made thousands of subscriptions. During the work of service, I designed three versions of it, also engaged in frontend development (JS framework, CSS and HTML);
- Instagram account management service, which served more than a thousand profiles and worked for more than three years. I was responsible for design and frontend.

# UX/UI Designer at EPAM

MAY 2011 - MAR 2014, Gomel

Worked on B2B design projects, especially on Cvent — service for group hotel reservations, that provides management, email marketing, and web surveys.

- Providing wireframes and prototypes;
- Making responsible web design;
- Interacting with a development team, planning and tracking deadlines;
- Communication with customers at meetings.

#### **SKILLS**

Product Design

User Experience

User Inteface Design

Interaction Design

Prototyping

Research

Usability testing

Design System maintainer

Wireframing

#### **TOOLS & TECHNOLOGIES**

Figma

Sketch

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe After Effects

Miro

Git

#### OTHER SKILLS

HTML

CSS

JS

SQL

PHP

#### **LANGUAGES**

Russian (Native)

English (B2)

#### ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

# UX/UI Design courses at IT Academy

2018-2019, Minsk

Taking courses on improving UX skills with a practicing art director. Two successfully completed projects: team and personal. The personal project Medok (mobile telemedicine service) received excellent marks.

### Development courses at EPAM

2011-2012, Gomel

Completing frontend and backend courses with senior EPAM developers.

- HTML, CSS, JS;
- Java, PHP.

#### **EDUCATION**

### Specialist's Degree in Software IT

2007-2012, Gomel

Francisk Skorina Gomel State University